ellad2.com 2016-11-17

# Privacy policy - Beading Tutorials and Patterns by Ellad2

**Personal information**

Ellad2.com respects your privacy. In general, you can visit Ellad2.com without telling me who you are or revealing any information about yourself.  You can register yourself on Ellad2.com but it is not necessary.

I want that my customers don’t have to give a lot of information before they are able to buy something. There are times, however, when I may need information from you, such as your e-mail address. It is my intent to let you know before I collect personal information from you.

If you choose to give me personal information that I may need to correspond with you or to send you a Tutorial, it is my intent to let you know how I will use this information. If you tell me that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.

Information collected by Ellad2.com is used internally by authorized Ellad2.com employees for three main purposes. First, we collect information to determine how to improve our site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular. Second, we collect information in order to personalize the site for my customers. For example, in the future, I may recommend products or features you may like based on what you have liked in the past. Lastly, we keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. **I do not sell, rent, share, loan, or transfer any personal information regarding my customers or subscribers to any third parties.**

 **Cookies**  
There are various technologies, including one called “cookies”, which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some Ellad2.com pages ( for example Paypal) use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. For example, we use these cookies for your shopping carttrack your clicks as you go through the Ellad2 site, to keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, to tell us whether you have visited Ellad2.com previously, and to help us determine whether you came to Ellad2.com from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

 **Security**  
The Ellad2.com website is hosted on a secure server. All information is stored on secure servers behind a firewall designed to deny unauthorized access.

 **Changes to this document**  
Changes to this document may be made time to time without warning. Ellad2 may or may not notify you of changes in this policy. Any changes made will be posted here.
